/**
 * @type {{
*  question: string,
*  answers: [ string, string ] | [ string, string, string ] | [ string, string, string, string ],
*  correct: number,
*  time: number
* }[] }
*/
export const questions = [
   {
       question: "When should you reach out for help?",
       answers: [
           "As soon as possible",
           "Only the day before class",
           "Day of class"
       ],
       correct: 0,
       time: 20
   },
   {
       question: "What photo editing software did we use the MOST?",
       answers: [
           "Pixler X",
           "Photopea",
           "Pixler E",
           "Adobe Lightroom"
       ],
       correct: 1,
       time: 20
   },
   {
       question: "Mr. Bonner normally came to class with a cup of what?",
       answers: [
           "Cofee",
           "Tea",
           "Water"
       ],
       correct: 2,
       time: 20
   },
   {
        question: " What are the Dutch wooden shoes called?",
        answers: [
            "Wood shoes",
            "Clogs",
            "Dutch slip-ons",
        ],
        correct: 1,
        time: 20
   },
   {
    question: " What base number system is composed of just zeros and ones?",
    answers: [
        "Base-0",
        "Base-1",
        "Base-10",
        "Base-2",
    ],
    correct: 3,  
    time: 20
   },
   {
    question: "In 1952 what computer predicted the outcome of the U.S election?",
    answers: [
        "Altair 8800",
        "Univac",
        "Altair 8000",
        "Pilot ACE",
    ],
    correct: 1,
    time: 20
   },
   {
    question: "How important is color when editing a picture?",
    answers: [
        "Very important", 
        "Ehhh doesn't make much a difference",
        "Not at all",
    ],
    correct: 0,
    time: 20
   }, 
   {
    question: "What year was the Altair 8800 made?",
    answers: [
        "1970",
        "1975",
        "1980",
        "1985",
    ],
    correct: 1,
    time: 20
   },
   {
    question: "When did Microsoft start?",
    answers: [
        "1950s",
        "1960s",
        "1970s",
        "1980s",
    ],
    correct: 2,
    time: 20
   },
   {
    question: "How good is your guessing?",
    answers: [
        "",
        "",
        "",
        "",
    ],
    correct: 3,
    time: 30
   }

  ]

